

JAY PATEL WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

- **9** +91 932 847 3489
- **1** jay64441860@gmail.com
- 🦸 jay.patel.112
- __jay.xi
- jaypatel3382
- in jaypatel1122
- jaypatel_1510
- 🕹 Bochasan, 388140

EDUCATION

Jul 2006 - Mar 2019

Completed Pre - Primary,
Primary (1-8), Secondary (9 &
SSC) and Higher Secondary (11
& HSC)

P. Chandra Vidhya Vihar School, Borsad

Aug 2019 - Present

Pursuing Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology field

Madhuben & Bhanubhai Instutite of Technology, GTU university

EXPERIENCE

Jun 2022 - Jul 2022

21 days Intership: Appointed as Backend Developer (NodeJS & ExpressJS)

AkashTechnolabs, Ahmedabad

Jan 2023 - Present

Working as a Intern in a Technology named ReactJS

Tech Elecon Pvt. Ltd, Vallabh Vidhyanagar

LANGUAGES

English	85%
Hindi	70%
Gujarati	95%

PROFILE

Hey..!! I'm Jay Patel from Bochasan. Currently, I am pursuing 8th sem of Bachelor of Engineering in IT field at MBIT college located in New Vidhyanagar. This is one of the best college in Gujarat. I have been started my Journey of my Engineering life in this college since 2019.

My full Name is Jay Mineshbhai Patel. I'm an Enthusiastic, Self-Motivated, Reliable, Responsible & Hard Working Person. I use a creative approach to solve the problem. I am motivated to go to the gym before work to get fit and healthy. My father is doing local Business of DC as well as Submersible motors (Servicing & Maintenance part). My Aim is to do Master of Engineering at US University.

PROJECTS

2020	BEAUTIFUL SNAKE GAME	JAVA, JAVA-FX	2 0
2020	ANIMATED CALCULATOR	HTML, CSS, JS	2 0
2021	AMAZING TIC-TAC-TOE GAME	HTML, CSS, JS	2 0
2021	GOOGLE KEEP CLONE APP	HTML, CSS, JS	2 0
2021	AWESOME CLOCK DESIGN	HTML, CSS, JS	2 0
2022	ATTRACTIVE LOGIN-SIGNUP WEBSITE	ANGULAR JS	മ് റ
2022	DATA ENTRY & SORTING	ANGULAR JS	2 0
2022	CALCULATOR APP	REACT JS	2 0
2022	WEATHER APP	REACT JS	B 0
2022	WEATHER APP	NODE JS, EXPRESS JS	2 0
2022	NOTES APP	REACT JS	2 0
2022	ANIMATED TODO APP	REACT JS, REDUX	2 0
2022	CRUD APP	MERN STACK	2 0
2022	REGISTRATION & LOGIN	MERN STACK	2 0
2022	CRUD APP	REACT JS & FIREBASE	2 0
2022	REGISTRATION & LOGIN	REACT JS & FIREBASE	2 0
2022	ANIMATED UI	REACT NATIVE	2 0
2022	TODO APP	REACT NATIVE	2 0
2022	AUTH APP	MERN STACK (NATIVE)	2 0
2023	CHATIFY	MERN STACK	് റ

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS



AREA OF INTEREST

••• Gaming	Cricket	Coding
₩ Fitness	₹ Riding	⅓ Hiking